const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ἀποκαλύπτω',
    answers: ['ik openbaar'],
    explanation: '(Apocalyps)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'κρύπτω',
    answers: ['ik verberg'],
    explanation: '(crypte, cryptogram)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'βαπτίζω',
    answers: ['ik doop'],
    explanation: '(baptist)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐγγιζω',
    answers: ['ik nader'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐλπίζω',
    answers: ['ik hoop'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'καθαρίζω',
    answers: ['ik reinig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'καθίζω',
    answers: ['ik zet', 'ik zit'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'σκανδαλίζω',
    answers: ['ik doe wankelen', 'ik erger', 'ik schandaliseer'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἁγιάζω',
    answers: ['ik heilig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'αγοράζω',
    answers: ['ik koop'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'βαστάζω',
    answers: ['ik draag'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δοξάζω',
    answers: ['ik verheerlijk'],
    explanation: '(doxologie)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑτοιμάζω',
    answers: ['ik bereid voor'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'θαυμάζω',
    answers: ['ik sta verbaasd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πειράζω',
    answers: ['ik test', 'ik toets', 'ik bekoor'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'κράζω',
    answers: ['ik roep'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'κηρύσσω',
    answers: ['ik verkondig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πράσσω',
    answers: ['ik doe'],
    explanation: '(praktijk)',
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'φυλάσσω',
    answers: ['ik bewaak'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson22Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson22-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 22 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson22Vocabulary
